I'll call it over to the Mama's Special Utility Authority Board meeting for Tuesday, January 17th, 2023.
We'll have the invocation by our new Deputy Varchee, Mr. Chris, Generalist.
Heavenly Father, we're thankful for you and the way that you love us, the way you provide for us,
we're blessed to have the opportunity to come in.
We have part of these meetings and I say that the discussion had tonight will be honest and respectful,
we'll have a little protective for the community, we'll just be with our leaders who willingly serve on this Council
and give them guidance and courage and knowledge to make the decisions that need to be made.
It's in your name we pray. Amen.
Thank you for the opportunity to do the live of the United States of America and to the
Republic for which it stands, one nation, under God, and invisible with the liberty and
defense of our own.
Number four, public input on scheduled personal appearances.
Five, continue to.
Staff recommends we approve item six and seven, two, two, two, three, four, seven,
very high.
Aye.
Eight, Gnail Stratten, Edmunds, and Palmer Claim for GRDA Realizing Thing in the amount
of $8,171.50.
Mayor, mayors of the council, the claim that's from your package tonight for the $8,171.50.
He is primarily for the time spent from November 21st to December 20th, on behalf of the
city where they focused on the ongoing legal process, including the review of the recent
GRDA and FERC filings and the proper response.
So this was time we spent in reviewing the response from the last study session, and then the
final response is that had to be submitted to FERC.
There was quite a bit of work that went into that, and, of course, Gnail Stratten operates as
a consultant on that project.
And for the record that is not the civil lawsuit, in this case, it is absolutely just related
to the relationship.
Make a motion, we approve.
Say it.
Aye.
So, hold on.
Senator, say.
Aye.
permits. The rolloff rental set of delivery. I believe we have a $10,000 max on that and
the pervite billings inspection fees, billing permit and the inspection fees. We want to
go no more than 1,200 on that and that includes any re-inspection that they may have.
Travis, this is a solid waste company other than the city mine is used to be in the social
office. If they use the rolloff for somebody else. This is only for the city of
Miami rolloffs and tipping fees. The tipping fees wave, yes. He can use a different rolloff and
that would have the tipping fees wave. If they use columns or whatever, we'll wait the tipping
fees for any demolition. I can't wait for the rolloff, but if they use that, we'll
wait for the rolloff. We'll make a motion now for a second.
Thank you.
Any other new business that has risen since the posting of this agenda? 11 staff reports, 12 trusty
community announcements, 13 adjournment.
Thank you.